Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): An associate editor at The Washington Post is going after Missouri Senator Josh Hawley, accusing the conservative Republican of being a, quote, manhood-obsessed hypocrite in an op-ed titled Josh Hawley's Problem with Masculinity. In the piece, Jonathan Capehart vilifies Hawley and claims that he is advocating for masculinity based on racial resentment. He wrote this, but as clownish as Hawley comes across, we dismiss him at our own risk. He is selling a vision
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): of masculinity to white America that has more to do with prejudice than manliness. Harris, they always come up with a new, more far-fetched liberal lunacy. I mean, this is another example. It's all about prejudice, apparently. Yeah,
Speaker 2: everything comes down to race. I'm not exactly sure how this does in this occasion, but I get it because the R word is what gets everybody's attention. So when did masculinity turn out to be such a horrible thing? them.
Speaker 2: did femininity turn out to be because i always think that if you hate one thing then you must hate the other right so i don't understand how we got to the point in this day and age of talking about masculinity and femininity when we are talking about pronouns and everything else so it comes down to race it comes down to gender and these are all ways to cancel people and i say just step away and and apparently
Speaker 3: he
Speaker 4: has because he's been pretty quiet
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): has been We do have a resident expert on masculinity who happens to be in the middle seat.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): it is it's funny because i
Speaker 5: married a woman who grew up on a dairy farm so i'm actually more of like a housewife but uh no i get it and i'm with holly on this one and you know this is the frustration okay masculinity is why we're here in the overall scheme of things we're here as a free country because our grandparents stormed the beach and saved private ryan this generation is watching private ryan and complaining that the cast isn't inclusive enough you know what i mean But the thing is, when you try to break this down
Speaker 5: racial lines this is the real hustle because minority children suffer from a strong male presence in the home at a much higher rate than anybody else so if you're going to get out there and champion strong male role models it's only going to help communities as studies show across all racial barriers that's why when they say like oh you know race
Speaker 5: When you go to race now, everybody knows it's because you've lost the argument. You know, they say in comedy you're not supposed to open with your closer. Calling things racist in this day and age is the closer. And if you're opening with it, it means you don't have anything else. So I'm going Hawley. Even though he doesn't look terribly masculine, he's got very pretty hair. But
Speaker 7: I'm just saying.
He
Speaker 8: does. You do too.
I
Speaker 7: mean, I'm pretty enough, you know, but I got a makeup team. Hawley's full-time pretty. He's a snack.
Speaker 8: He's
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): pretty in that suit. He's a snack. Oh, my gosh. Laura, Senator Hawley, I mean, what a conservative rock star. I got to interview him at Turning Point. -
Right.
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): guys going after big tech, he told me, you know, Afghanistan, that's something that's going to be investigated in a Republican Congress. I think that's at the root of the problem
Speaker 9: is he's one of the best and brightest in our party, in my view. Oh, yeah. Well, they always go after. I look the way they went after my father-in-law, look at the way they go after Ron DeSantis. Senator Hawley is no different, obviously. But, Jimmy, I love
Speaker 10: the point you brought up when I was reading this. And by the way, it's The Washington Post. So let's take it all with a huge grain of salt, everything that they've said in there.
Speaker 10: All I could think about was my grandfather who fought in World War II and the men that died young and old to form our country. And they're the reason that our society has been able to progress truly as much as we have so that we have individuals at The Washington Post able to write such ridiculous columns like this. It is because of masculinity. Harris, I agree with you. When did it become a bad thing? We need men in our society. We need women in our society. We need everybody. We do. We need everyone. We need fathers.
Speaker 10: in the home for children, Jimmy, like you're saying. And I just think it's so crazy to try and attack something that actually has been very beneficial in such a huge part, truly, of our history. If
Speaker 12: you don't appreciate our men, then I doubt that you appreciate
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): our women. That's probably true. You know, the Washington Post, democracy dies in darkness, they say. Well, common sense dies in darkness, and we're putting light on this, but this toxic masculinity nonsense, it's everywhere. And
Speaker 13: really, I think the yardage claimed...
Speaker 13: by this op-ed was really astounding it was like 20 football fields and what i mean by that is the lengths that this author went to and inciting another author as well in deconstructing and pushing holly into a box and then they had the nerve to do exactly the same thing that they were accusing him of which was being unwielding right so they said you know incidentally jason candor presents a refreshing version of masculinity um that views vulnerability vulnerability as a virtue you can be the best man one can be for one's family and community. No, that's exactly what
Josh
Speaker 13: holly's doing that's exactly what masculinity is is through that strength being the best man you can be so here are they saying that instead aversion to labor organizing support exclusively for heterosexual marriage i mean they were in the weeds here absolutely attacking this man for daring to put forth his faith and his vision of masculinity and they're saying the exact same things that he did i find it preposterous um and really curious that anyone would accept this argument whatsoever yeah and
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): their issues like labor organizing these are all code for liberalism i mean so that's at the root of this is he's not a liberal and therefore the washington post is going to write hit pieces well done i guess